<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-12T09:14:14+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome Laura-Jane</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recruitment/2019/09/04/welcome-laura-jane.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome Laura-Jane" /><published>2019-09-04T12:41:31+01:00</published><updated>2019-09-04T12:41:31+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recruitment/2019/09/04/welcome-laura-jane</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recruitment/2019/09/04/welcome-laura-jane.html">&lt;p&gt;With the steady increase in incoming work, we’ve been looking for multiple new additions for the Cargo team. We’re pleased to say we’ve found some and this week we’re shouting about Laura-Jane, our new digital marketing executive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Who are you?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laura-Jane Todd&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Where are you from?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cramlington&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What experience are you bringing to Cargo?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent some time volunteering on the St Oswald’s marketing and comms team whilst at university before specialising in digital marketing at a large North East agency where I worked for almost two years. My role involved creating on-site and off-site copy and helping deliver digital marketing strategies for a range of clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What are you looking forward to achieving at Cargo?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking forward to being involved with creating some exciting digital marketing strategies and getting to know the clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What do you enjoy doing outside of work?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I’m not at work I’m usually listening to podcasts, catching up on the latest binge-worthy shows on Netflix, discovering food places around Newcastle and travelling to new places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How have you found your first two weeks at Cargo?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone at Cargo has been very welcoming and made me feel part of the team!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How is your Great North Run training going and who are you running for?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following a few initial injuries, it’s going well! I’m running with my friend, we’re up to ten miles with a week to go and we’ve reached our fundraising target. I’m raising money for St Oswald’s Hospice who provide amazing support for those living with incurable conditions and their families which is keeping me motivated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">With the steady increase in incoming work, we’ve been looking for multiple new additions for the Cargo team. We’re pleased to say we’ve found some and this week we’re shouting about Laura-Jane, our new digital marketing executive!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome Matt</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recruitment/2019/08/27/welcome-to-matt.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome Matt" /><published>2019-08-27T14:41:31+01:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T14:41:31+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recruitment/2019/08/27/welcome-to-matt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recruitment/2019/08/27/welcome-to-matt.html">&lt;p&gt;With the steady increase in incoming work, we’ve been looking for multiple new additions for the Cargo team. We’re pleased to say we’ve found some and this week we’re shouting about Matt, our new front-end developer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Who are you?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew Oliver Proctor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Where are you from?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coventry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What experience are you bringing to Cargo?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am bringing a varied knowledge base to the role having worked with clients of different sizes in a multitude of sectors. I have created websites for FedEx/TNT and The Heart of England Co-operative, along with helping small business establish their online presences and I am sure this will prove valuable to our upcoming projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What are you looking forward to achieving at Cargo?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking forward being part of the Cargo team creating amazing web sites for our clients and their customers. I am also hoping to create innovative interactive experiences by developing my skills through hard work and learning new technologies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What do you enjoy doing outside of work?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside of work I am a huge comedy and sports fan. I also love to travel, visiting different cultures and experiencing new adventures while sampling whatever local food and drink is on offer as I go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How have you found your first two weeks at Cargo?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cargo team as a whole have been very friendly and welcoming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How do you think Cov is going to perform this season?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the first couple of games are anything to go by we are in for a good season, but knowing Coventry we will be in the playoffs at Christmas and in a relegation fight come May. It’s a painful existence supporting The Sky Blues but hopefully this season will be the light at the end of a very long tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">With the steady increase in incoming work, we’ve been looking for multiple new additions for the Cargo team. We’re pleased to say we’ve found some and this week we’re shouting about Matt, our new front-end developer!</summary></entry></feed>